<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FitSpo</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps"></string>
    <string name="promoter_prompt">We\'re glad you love our app! Now please rate us in the app store!</string>
    <string name="detractor_prompt">We\'re sorry you\'re experiencing problems with our app, we promise to address the issues you experienced as quickly as possible.</string>
    <string name="error_prompt">SM SDK Error - see logs</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to our University Student Health App: FitSpo! FitSpo is an app created by three UNSW students with a passion for student wellbeing, and maintaining a healthy student lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="modules">FitSpo has a number of modules that you can complete which will unlock special offers from UNSW that can be claimed on campus!</string>
    <string name="special_offers">After you pass a module, a special offer from UNSW will be unlocked. To access special offers, click the Special Offers icon at the bottom of the home screen!</string>

    <string name="exercise_content1">The article below from Health Direct Australia outlines the importance of daily physical activity - not only for physical but also for mental health.</string>
    <string name="exercise_content2">The goal of 10,000 steps is the recommended daily step target for healthy adults. This goal encourages the accumulation of incidental activity throughout the whole day.\n\n*Read the article below carefully, as the final module quiz is reliant on the content below!</string>

    <string name="module_return">Return to Module</string>
    <string name="menu_return">Return to Menu</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="start_quiz">Start Quiz</string>

    <string name="back4app_server_url">https://zlemura.back4app.io//</string>
    <!-- Change the following strings as required -->
    <string name="back4app_app_id">XUJAc2oV4izfGJCo2zlyrGaHRcgetESRCE124CpE</string>
    <string name="back4app_client_key">VmhChcTgTvOEhv5pNk6BvGzL57IimdLiw1jDVVO5</string>

    <string name="google_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">AIzaSyB6iw5s4YJZD2Dgw4uY8Ec53dfhy16sPJE</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
